bovadapromotions.lv 2019-12-31

# Privacy Policy and Overview - Play Online Poker | Bovada

## PRIVACY POLICY

This policy describes the way in which Bovada.lv (otherwise referred to herein as “we” or “us” or “the Website”) deals with the information and data provided by you to enable us to manage and maintain your relationship with us.

### COLLECTED INFORMATION

If you set up an Account on the Website, you will be asked for personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, email address, phone number, etc. That same information, plus credit card or other deposit information, will be requested if you elect to conduct transactions through the Website.

We may also collect details of your visits to the Website and use of its services. This data may include, but is not limited to, details of your web browser, location and IP address.

Some of the services and [special features](https://www.bovada.lv/contents/bovada-just-better) that are offered on the Website require you to provide information as a condition of usage. These services include access to participation in sweepstakes or contests, and access to subscription-only areas (if any). You may always choose not to provide personally identifiable information, but this may lead to decreased functionality of the Website for you, and/or the inability to provide you with certain products or services. If you complete a transaction on our Website using a credit card, the credit card processor may collect your information.

### USE OF INFORMATION

By setting up your account and any use of the Website and its services (either directly or through use of any app used to access your account) confirms your consent to the use of your personal information as set out in this policy. If you do not agree with the terms herein then you must immediately discontinue your use of the Website and its services.

Your personally identifiable information will not be sold or rented to anyone.

Personally identifiable information about you will made available to the Website owner, and your personally identifiable information will be provided to other companies or people only when and if: (1) you have given your consent to share the information; (2) your information is to be shared to provide the service or information you have requested; (3) to respond to any legal process(es); (4) it is determined that you violated any Website Terms of Service other usage guidelines or rules for specific services; or (5) for identity verification purposes as outlined in Section 3.6 of the Terms of Service. Unless you are notified to the contrary at the time of collection, any companies or entities to which we provide information under point #2 above are limited to using that information only to the degree necessary to provide the service or information you have requested.

Also, users who create an account on the Website may receive a "Welcome" email, containing valuable account information and "Service Announcements", such as important messages concerning any temporary site or system outages, plus any maintenance issues that may affect the level of service. In order to provide the information or services you have requested, your identifiable information may be transferred or stored on computer equipment or in offices that are located outside the European Economic Area, and you are deemed to consent to the same.

### COOKIES

By setting up an account or by your continued use of the website you agree to our use of Cookies.

Cookies, clear GIFs, and other technology to track how and when visitors use the Website may be used. Cookies make web surfing easier by saving your passwords and other preferences for you, and identify the IP address of your computer.

Cookies also help identify which areas of the Website are popular and which are not, which may then be used to improve the user experience on the Website. You can set your browsers to reject cookies and cookies are not necessary to visit the Website; however, some functions and services will not be available unless you enable cookies on your browser.

### SECURITY AND PRIVACY

Reasonable steps have been undertaken to manage the privacy of your personally identifiable information and the security of this Website. 

The transmission of information over the internet is not completely secure. We will always do our best to protect your information however we cannot guarantee the security of the information that you disclose online. For your own protection we advise that you do not provide your account credentials to anyone. We will never ask for your password. 

The Website may contain links to other websites that are owned and operated by third parties. The information practices of those other websites are not covered by this Policy. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of other websites. We strongly suggest that you review such third party's privacy policies before providing any information to them. You should contact these entities directly with questions about their use of the information that they collect. 

### OPTING IN, OPTING OUT, AND MODIFYING INFORMATION

By opting to receive email from through the Website, you are opting in to receive by electronic mail information and/or offers on any new promotions, events, products or materials from our clients for whom we manage this policy.

If at any time you indicate that you no longer want to receive such email communications, or if you want to change or correct any previously provided information we maintain, you may send such direction to the contact information below and such changes will be made ASAP.

As a security precaution, we may ask that you provide identifying information such as name, address, and/or birth date in order to confirm your identity. In addition, access to personally identifiable information may be limited or denied where providing such access would be unreasonably burdensome or expensive in the circumstances, or as otherwise permitted by law.

### UPDATES

From time to time, this Privacy Policy may be updated. When and if this is done the "last updated" date in the Privacy Policy noted below will also be revised. By continuing to use this Website after posting of a new or updated Privacy Policy, you consent to the use of their personally identifiable information in accordance with the new policy. Opt-in consent for any updates to this Privacy Policy that materially expand the sharing or use of your personal information in ways not disclosed in this Privacy Policy will be obtained at the time of collection.

### INTEGRITY OF SPORT

Bovada is committed to ensuring the integrity of sport and to participating in efforts to identify and eradicate match fixing. As such, notwithstanding any other term of the Terms of Service, or any provision of the applicable Privacy Policy, by placing a bet or wager on the website, you expressly acknowledge and agree that Bovada at all times reserves the right in its sole discretion to report Irregular Betting Activity to such sports federations, regulators, agencies, commissions or associations (or their respective agents) as Bovada deems appropriate ("Regulatory Bodies") in order to enable identification of irregular activity and to support appropriate investigations. "Irregular Betting Activity" means activity that, in Bovada's sole assessment, deviates from expected betting patterns and includes, without limitation: (i) an unusual and significant number of bets originating from the same geographic region or through linked accounts; (ii) a bettor continuing to place bets at any price in the face of a steady reduction in the applicable odds; and/or (iii) any other indicator or pattern assessed by Bovada as indicative of potential match fixing. Bovada shall use reasonable commercial measures to ensure that any information provided to Regulatory Bodies pursuant to this provision is subject to reasonable contractual non-disclosure provisions, and that all information or documentation shall be destroyed by such Regulatory Bodies when it is no longer relevant in connection with any ongoing investigation, enquiry or disciplinary process.

Download our poker software and [play online poker](https://www.bovada.lv/poker/play-poker) today!

Last updated: February 22, 2018
